click.dj 2015-03-15

# Click.DJ - Manage Music

  1. Dashboard

#### DASHBOARD

[ Dashboard ](http://click.dj/manage)  Contact Us 

* * *

* * *

## Data Controller and Owner

MacroWish - Oranje Nassaulaan 31/2, 1075AJ Amsterdam (The Netherlands),  
contact@macrowish.com  

## Summarized Information

Summarized information listed below may be subject to change listed later in this Privacy Policy.

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name or email address. Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for). We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. Our service does not currently recognize the "Do Not Track" signal that may be available in some web browsers.

We do not use or collect your precise geographic location.

We may keep data indefinitely.

As for the third party social network connections (the 'apps' which you may be asked to connect to in order to download a song): Click.DJ doesn't use or manipulate any of the user data collected from the third party social website connections (Facebook, Twitter, SoundCloud, Instagram) other than to 'Follow' the user accounts that you have explicitly given consent to on any 'Download' page. The user accounts that you may follow on these networks are explicitly listed when clicking the 'Free Download' button. If you agree to the 'Follow & Download' dialog on any download page and have connected to the social media apps you will automatically follow the accounts listed.

Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. 

In order to serve you, we may share your personal and anonymous information with other companies, including vendors and contractors. Their use of information is limited to these purposes, and subject to agreements that require them to keep the information confidential. Our vendors provide assurance that they take reasonable steps to safeguard the data they hold on our behalf, although data security cannot be guaranteed. Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that Click.DJ collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Usage Data. 

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using Click.DJ.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by Click.DJ or by the owners of third party services used by Click.DJ, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for Click.DJ to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through Click.DJ and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Method of processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.

### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.

## The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application / Website to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Access to third party services' accounts, Registration and authentication and Displaying content from external platforms. 

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

## Facebook permissions asked by Click.DJ

Click.DJ may ask some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User's Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it.

For more information about the following permissions, refer to the [Facebook permissions documentation](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/authentication/permissions/) and to the [Facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

The permissions asked are the following:

### Basic information

By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the user has made more of their data public, more information will be available.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  * ### Access to third party services' accounts

These services allow Click.DJ to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.  
These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.

#### Access to the Facebook account (Click.DJ)

This service allows Click.DJ to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

Permissions asked: . 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

#### Access to the Twitter account (Click.DJ)

This service allows Click.DJ to connect with the User's account on the Twitter social network, provided by Twitter Inc.

These services allow Click.DJ to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.  
Actions include automatically 'Following' a user after the authorizing user has given specific permission to do so by connecting their Twitter account to the Click.DJ App and confirming the 'Follow' action through a confirmation screen which is shown before the 'Follow' action is performed..

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

#### Access to the Instagram account (Click.DJ)

This service allows Click.DJ to connect with the User's account on the Twitter social network, provided by Instagram Inc.

These services allow Click.DJ to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.  
Actions include automatically 'Following' a user after the authorizing user has given specific permission to do so by connecting their Twitter account to the Click.DJ App and confirming the 'Follow' action through a confirmation screen which is shown before the 'Follow' action is performed..

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/#)

#### Access to the SoundCloud account (Click.DJ)

This service allows Click.DJ to connect with the User's account on the SoundCloud social network, provided by SoundCloud Inc.

These services allow Click.DJ to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.  
Actions include receiving information from the users' uploaded files and automatically 'Following' a user after the authorizing user has given specific permission to do so by connecting their SoundCloud account to the Click.DJ App and confirming the 'Follow' action through a confirmation screen which is shown before the 'Follow' action is performed.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy)

  * ### Displaying content from external platforms

These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of Click.DJ and interact with them.  
If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.

#### SoundCloud widget (SoundCloud Limited)

Soundcloud is an audio content delivery service provided by SoundCloud Limited that allows Click.DJ to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data. 

Place of processing : Germany – [Privacy Policy](https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy)

  * ### Registration and authentication

By registering or authenticating, Users allow Click.DJ to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.  
Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services.  
In this case, Click.DJ will be able to access and change some Data, stored by these third party services, for registration, identification, or other purposes ('Following' and 'Liking' users on Facebook, Twitter, and SoundCloud).

#### Twitter Oauth (Twitter)

Twitter Oauth is a registration and authentication service provided by Twitter Inc. and is connected to the Twitter social network.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data including Followers. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://dev.twitter.com/terms/api-terms)

#### SoundCloud Oauth (SoundCloud Limited)

SoundCloud Oauth is a registration and authentication service provided by SoundCloud Limited and is connected to the SoundCloud network.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data including Followers. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy)

#### Facebook Authentication (Facebook)

Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data including Pages Liked. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/help/?page=229348490415842)

#### Instagram Authentication (Instagram)

Instagram OAuth Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Instagram and is connected to the Instagram social network.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data including Pages Liked. 

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/#)

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of Click.DJ or the related services. 

### Additional Information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, Click.DJ may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data. 

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, Click.DJ and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application / Website (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address). 

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information. 

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above. 

Click.DJ does not support “do not track” requests.  
To understand if any of the third party services it uses honor the “do not track” requests, please read their privacy policies. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using Click.DJ and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users. 

### Information about this privacy policy

The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by macrowish and hosted on the macrowish's servers. 

###  Definitions and legal references 

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from Click.DJ (or third party services employed in Click.DJ ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use Click.DJ, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application / Website) and the details about the path followed within the Application / Website with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using Click.DJ, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.

#### Data Processor

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Application / Website Owner, or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application / Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of Click.DJ.

#### Click.DJ

The hardware or software tool by which the User Personal Data is collected.

* * *

#### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

This privacy policy is solely about Click.DJ.
